This is a plan that is about to
overturn the audience's perception.
The boys gather together
for their acting dreams.
Through various challenges
they will test each other
pull and push
and heat things up.
On the road to becoming actors
they will find their own chosen CP.
X
is edge
is vulnerability
and is emotion.
Y
is softness
is vulnerability
and is emotion.
When X and Y collide
an invisible magnetic field quietly turns.
The boys' bonds
are tied to each other.
This is not the established
formula of the masses.
This is a brand‑new coordinate system.
This is.
PROJECT XY
"Project XY"
(Episode 1: First meet
Hello XY)
(Who will be the first to appear?)
Still can't open it.
What's wrong?
Okay, it works now.
Hello everyone.
My name is Young.
I work in medical sales
and I also do some part‑time modeling.
Because I myself am also
optimistic and outgoing.
Who likes to
get along with everyone
and have fun with everyone.
My personal hobbies are playing guitar
and basketball.
Actually, I've always had
a dream of being an actor.
My reason for coming here is
to experience a different life
and meet new friends.
My ideal CP partner is
someone gentle
empathetic
and knows how to
take care of themselves.
Welcome to PROJECT XY.
In here, you will
go through many trials.
Together with your chosen one you
will perform a graduation performance.
Wishing all of you
a wonderful experience.
This is...
roommate info.
Hope you're tidy.
Remember to flush.
Without permission
no climbing onto my bed.
I notice that everyone seems
to like cleanliness.
(Looking around)
There's a letter.
Let me see what is it.
Please choose
any one ornament on the table
as your chosen item.
It will determine
the entry order of the next actor.
Let's see what this is.
Lollipops, a camera
and a Bluetooth headset.
I'll pick the lollipop
because I like eating lollipops.
I think it'll be
someone very enthusiastic
and cute.
(Looking forward to it)
probably like that.
Right.
Hello everyone.
My name is Tyler.
I graduated from the Central Academy of
Drama with a major in Acting.
Since graduation
I've been working as an actor
I came to this show because.
I think it's fun
There's no show like this before.
It involves my profession
and I have to find a CP
so the format feels
very fresh to me.
I have a low threshold for laughter.
And also a low crying threshold.
But I'm the type
who gets sulky easily
yet if you coax me
I'll cheer up right away.
Ideally, my partner
would be sporty in appearance
likes sports
a sporty style.
In personality
I hope he's a
empathetic person.
At first sight
if I like someone
and feel we can click
I'll give 100% of myself..
Hello.
Are you the only one here?
Yeah, just me right now.
Because I picked your item.
This lollipop was left by you.
Yes.
Give it to me.
Just sit here.
We can sit anywhere, right?
Yeah.
You brought a backpack.
Yes.
Did they tell you what to do?
No.
Just to pick an item
I studied them for a while
some I didn't even recognise.
I don't even know your name yet
I'm Young.
Young?
Yes.
Which yang?
The yang in
"dang yang" (rippling)
I'm Tyler.
Tang of the Tang Dynasty.
Ge as in pavilion.
Yuan as in far.
This name.
Your name sounds nice.
Yes.
I even checked online
no one else
has the same name. (Little Pride)
Tyler is nice.
Although it's a bit different
from what I imagined
but he is cute.
It should be true,
I just believe the Internet.
Then I...
I'll pick one...
Yes, You need to pick one
I'll pick.
Empty?
Pick one
I pick this one.
Camera.
You like photography?
Yes, I like taking photos of others.
You do?
Yes.
Because I myself
emmmm…
get very stiff in photos
super awkward.
You're shy?
Not shy
just awkward. (Awkwardly
speaking in dialect)
Where are you from?
Henan.
Have you looked around?
I only saw the first floor.
I didn't dare go up to the second floor.
Why?
Because it's look dark up there. (Shy)
(awkward)
Then let's wait.
Do you want some?
Now?
Can I eat it?
Just eat.
Why not?
Anyway, it's mine.
Eat it.
Alright.
You open it.
When I was little
I used to crush it.
Wait a bit.
Okay.
Why aren't they coming?
No rush.
I just took a walk too.
Look, you can see this.
Here's a roommate rule sheet
Let me tell you.
All of our roommates
seem like said
"they like it clean."
Which one is mine?
I wrote several myself.
But I can't find mine.
I wrote...
"love cleanliness"
and the second one
is also mine.
These two should be mine
number ten and eleven.
Just sit and wait.
At first
I picked the lollipop
thinking it would be
someone cute.
Me?
I'm fine with anything
as long as it's candy.
You like sweets?
I thought you picked it
except you,
everyone else could have candy.
I thought you were quite thoughtful.
Turns out it was random.
You over-thought.
Let's wait.
Hello everyone
my name is Waner.
I run a pet store.
I came to this show because
I'm very interested in
the acting industry.
I hope to break out
of my shell a bit
not to be so
introverted.
For my CP partner
I'd like someone outgoing
and cheerful.
I hope to get along well with everyone.
And I'm really looking forward
to meeting everyone.
Hope
I can
quickly fit in.
Hello.
Here's a candy for you.
Thanks.
A welcome gift.
This is yours, right?
Yes, mine.
So you like photography?
I can take photos for you.
Same as me.
I'm Tyler.
He's.
Young.
Yanwu Xu.
Xu as in wish
and Yang as in rippling.
I'm Waner.
You can call me Waner.
Waner?
Wan Zhewei.
Zhewei, wanwan.
Which one is yours?
Definitely one
they just reworded it.
Yes, it's there...
Which one is yours?
The last one.
So you're an I‑person?
Very I.
Yeah, I can tell.
What's your MBTI?
I'm INFJ.
INFJ
And you?
ENFP
You?
ENFJ
Big sword bro.
Zodiac?
I'm Leo.
Fire sign.
Fire sign Green Old Man.
I'm also fire.
Sagittarius.
You?
Scorpio.
(Like oil and water)
Okay.
Sorry.
Because he picked your token.
Your token is.
The camera.
So you came out.
Then.
Now you have to pick one from these.
So I pick another one?
Yes, pick one.
These?
These three.
What's this one?
I don't recognise it.
Picture board.
Pigment pan?
I was thinking about that.
Then I'll pick the palette.
Okay.
I'll take this.
Alright.
Just put it there.
Like this?
It should be so.
(Silence is tonight's Cambridge)
Here he comes.
Hello everyone.
I'm Elio, Zhang Chijie.
I'm a commercial actor.
I came to this show to
experience group living.
My ideal CP partner
is someone
who can be both a mentor and a friend
with a complementary personality.
A note to my future self
I hope you enjoy
this journey.
Hello.
Hello
I brought you all some gifts.
So thoughtful.
Thanks.
Inside is Cantonese herbal tea.
You're from Guangdong?
(line up to welcome)
Yes, and also
spray, and?
Mosquito repellent.
So this palette is yours?
Yes, it's mine.
You dress like a painter too.
You like drawing?
Yes, because I'm an art student.
The palette
it feels like me
with different emotions
like different colours
mixing together
to form who I am.
I'm Tyler.
Tyler.
And I'm Young, Yanwu Xu.
Yanwu Xu.
Young.
Tyler.
You can call me Waner.
OK, I'm Elio.
Call me Elio.
So you're an E‑person?
No, I'm an I‑person.
You're an I?
I'm INFJ.
Both of you are?
You're IN-
I'm INFJ.
I'm also a little green person.
No, Green Old Man.
But he seems like an E.
Who, me?
You seem very E.
Okay.
So where did you get the candy?
That's mine – I'll share later.
Sorry.
Where is my candy?
Why do you three have candy
and I don't?
Sorry, here's yours.
I'll eat later.
A gift?
No, it's my item.
Because I like
and my surname is Tang (sweet)
(Happy to have candy)
Yes.
P‑people
can only accept their plans
being disrupted.
Aren't you accept
your plans being disrupted?
Must be planned.
Like if you plan to do
you definitely do it then.
That's fine.
Do you two do that?
No?
You do?
Yeah.
Okay.
You're really I.
XY roommate info.
Which one is yours?
Let me see.
Guess?
(Thinking carefully)
You're INFJ, right?
Actually, I'm okay with anything
I think I am, too.
Which is your hard requirement?
I'm number twelve.
I guessed it.
How did you know?
Me?
I'll guess you're...
number thirteen?
Right.
You?
Number five?
No.
I'm "enthusiastic and not boring".
You?
Number one?
No.
You're nine?
Yes?
Yes.
Yes, I'll guess yours.
You're...
You should be
nine
or three?
Neither.
Then you're eleven?
Close
but that's not mine.
Mine is similar.
Nine, ten, eleven are all mine.
Alright.
Now you can choose
from these two items
only these two left.
You have to pick one.
Have to pick one.
I pick the earphones.
What's that for?
The owner of this item
is the next person to come.
(So that's how it is!)
He is the first person?
He is the first person.
You're the first person.
Yes.
So you...
He picked the candy and chose me.
So you don't have anything?
I have
this is mine.
So where are you guys from?
I'm from Guangdong.
No wonder you wear that.
I didn't wear this.
It's for my cat.
I have a cat
and I put this on its collar.
Because my cat has been
with me a long time.
So I wanted to
bring one of its items.
When I miss him,
I can look at it.
I'm from Guangdong
but my hometown is Hunan.
Though I don't eat spicy food.
You don't?
Because I'm used to Cantonese flavor.
Me too.
The next person seems to be coming.
Is he coming?
Hello everyone, my name is Joel
I'm a recent college graduate.
I really want to experience
a life different from before.
I also want to explore
my own potential.
I'm a gentle person
with rich emotions.
I think I'm very empathetic.
My ideal CP
is someone
who can gently
hold my emotions.
This time I hope to find find
my own unique warm light here.
Hello.
Sit down.
Sit.
Here's a gift.
Thanks.
It's herbal tea.
Because I'm from Guangdong.
You brought a gift?
So what's your name?
Call me Joel.
Joel.
Elio.
Young.
Tyler.
And...
Waner.
So your MBTI is...
Green Old Man?
That's INFJ.
Three of them.
It's INFJ.
You're ENFJ.
Where are you from?
I'm from Sichuan.
You're from Guangdong.
He's also from Guangdong.
Me too.
You're from Guangdong.
Guess about him.
We're from Henan.
Northerners.
Did you go look around?
No, I just...
I just sat here
I read the roommate rules.
Which one is yours?
You're number nine?
No, number nine isn't you.
Number nine should be you.
Sorry, teacher.
It's okay.
Mine is very simple.
I just wrote one line.
I think it's all the same.
Normal points.
When making contact with friends.
All the key points should be covered.
So which one is yours?
Young is a bit...
a bit mysterious.
I feel...
I'm curious.
Maybe because
he's also from Guangdong.
We're fellow townspeople.
So where are we going?
Let's...
Let's go outside and have a look.
Someone else?
There's a box.
I really like skateboarding.
It feels free.
So I brought it here.
Hello everyone
I'm CH.
I'm a theatre actor.
I came here
to meet like
minded people.
I'm an Aquarius.
So I stick to "free"
all the way.
My chosen CP is someone
humorous, passionate
and with shared interests.
My reaction
might be a few beats
slower than others.
But
once I've decided on someone
I will without hesitation
walk towards him.
Hello.
Hello everyone.
Good afternoon.
(turn up the corners of their mouths)
I'm CH.
Call me CH.
Huanhuan.
Yes.
OK
Please sit, have a seat.
I just got this box outside.
Shall we open it
and read together？
Sure.
So, aren't you curious
what the five of us are called?
Let's introduce ourselves first.
Sit down and chat.
Okay, sit.
Call me Joel.
Elio, Zhang with a bow.
Call me Young or Yangyang.
OK
Tyler.
Call me Tyler.
I'm Waner.
Call me Waner.
Alright, OK.
Got it?
Repeat it again.
It's hard, it's hard.
But it's okay.
We'll remember later.
Just kidding.
Let's look at the card.
Wait.
We'll get to know each other later.
It's too hard for me.
Just kidding, just kidding.
Let's see this first.
This
here's a mission card.
Each person
chooses one red string.
The two who draw the same string
will automatically be matched
as XY heart‑choice roommates.
So we're drawing rooms.
Where?
Here.
Seems we each
pick an end.
I'll pull this longest one.
Three.
Two.
One.
Pull.
Okay.
You.
We're roommates.
He and I.
(Peek)
That move came so fast.
My brain hadn't even
processed it yet.
Someone already
took a string
and we drew
I just pulled one
I didn't have any
scenario in mind.
It's fate.
Just let it be.
Not a coincidence, would I?
Actually, when I first came in.
I felt I’d like to pick
Waner as my roommate.
It’s just a vibe.
I'm happy.
For CH.
I think he's...
He‘s also
quite "I" too.
But I feel we'll
have a lot to talk about.
It's fine
I didn't overthink it.
This is fate.
I think
going forward
I'm more looking forward to
what sparks
we'll create together.
And then
for each matched pair,
negotiation is required to
choose one representative
to compete in an elimination battle.
The winner and their roommate
in room selection
get absolute priority.
Let's go.
Go.
XY Heart‑Choice Room.
The matched pairs from
the previous round
must choose one representative
for an elimination tournament.
All representatives will
determine their match sequence
via "black‑white‑match".
Each duel is limited to 1 minute.
The selected player
must wrap the duvet
for more than 5 seconds.
The overall winner
get first choice of rooms.
Okay.
OK
Let's do black‑white‑match.
Black‑white‑match.
Come on.
Come on. Let's decide.
Okay.
Black‑white‑match.
Come on.
Three, two, one.
OK.
Okay, we go first.
We go first, right?
Yes, we go first.
Okay.
Fighting.
Come on.
Let me take your jacket.
Out of respect.
For our happiness, go!
Put it on the floor first, right?
We do our best.
Okay, we'll count down.
We'll count.
Okay.
Three.
Two.
One.
Yes, like this.
Like this.
It's okay.
Oh my god!
Like this!
Don't laugh.
Oh my god!
Slow down, slow down.
UFC
This is
like a naked choke.
Overwhelming victory.
It's okay.
Alright.
Nice!
We'll pick first.
We'll give them the first pick.
You're next...
Go ahead.
He's strong.
Come on!
You can beat him!
Okay.
You'll definitely be second.
Not necessarily.
If he wins this
then
we'll be last.
Just one more round
then we'll be last.
Fight， don't be nervous.
Why does everyone use that move?
Because we're too exposed.
Yes，if it is just...
Knees...
This is real competitive
spirit between men.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
OK
Good fight!
Your roommate is really going for it.
He won.
It's fine, we gave it our all.
We lost with honour.
We were great anyway.
Very impressive!
His neck is all red.
Looks like bruising.
This is our badge of honour
for just arriving.
The medal for newcomers here.
We gave it our all.
I want to play too.
It looked fun.
You want to play too?
Alright, come on.
No favouritism.
What is it going to do?
Three.
Two.
One.
Go.
Careful.
Got him!
Oh my god!
Take it.
See? You're like this...
They'll be roommates.
I think they suit each other.
Oh my god!
My partner might be done for.
Careful!
Oh my god!
Good fight!
Nice!
That was hard!
I think you win.
Champion.
Runner‑up.
And.
Third.
OK
Let's go.
Go.
Pick the rooms.
There are no numbers here.
Here.
This is one room.
Here is only two.
It's a four‑person room, guys.
Upstairs too.
Going up.
I guessed right.
Someone gets a whole floor.
This is Room 1.
Room 3.
See that?
Nice!
Number one is here.
This one's nice.
Guys, this is obviously
for the winner.
First pick – you choose first.
We choose this one.
Is there even a choice for us?
Let's wait.
I think we'll take the second floor.
We save climbing one floor.
We'll take the second floor.
Done We have the whole floor on the second.
Actually this is fine too.
We have the whole floor.
Alright.
I'm not pleased.
But I do hate myself
for not actively fighting
for it in the game
I'm a bit regretful.
They picked this.
We pick this.
Poor us!
It's his fault.
He's too good!
Let's check it out.
Let's go.
My luggage.
Yes, two 30‑inch suitcases.
Which floor are we?
We're on the third.
Yes, we're on the same floor as you.
Okay.
So funny.
Mine.
Let me help you pull this up.
Thanks.
We'll put it in the corner.
Let's just pile the suitcases here.
Suddenly I regret choosing the third floor.
Do you have more stuff?
Yes.
Still downstairs?
Thanks.
Which side do you want?
I sleep...
I'm fine with either, you choose.
Then I'll take the window side.
Okay.
Since graduation
this is my first living with a group.
I've always lived alone.
Just call me.
Give it to me, careful.
So heavy!
Let's do it together.
Look at my suitcase.
Your stuff is quite heavy.
It's okay.
Let me.
I'll lift from the side.
Third floor?
Third.
Let's do it again.
Group living feels
different from living alone.
Doing things together
with everyone.
Let's go.
This must be.
Tyler's stuff.
His suitcase is huge.
Why do I have so much?
You've got a lot in your bag?
Lotions and creams.
This.
Lotion.
This is, yes.
Cream.
Put it here.
By the way
you can draw, right?
How about we
make some house rules
for the next few days?
Sure.
Rules, OK?
Let's go downstairs.
Go.
Since we just met
and our time in the house
is limited
having a set of guidelines
can quickly
avoid some
unnecessary trouble.
I can't squat down?
Wearing shorts.
What were we going to do？
Make a plan?
Make rules.
Not "rules", but
"roommate living guidelines".
Do you remember?
I forgot.
Anyway he's okay with anything.
Yes, I'm flexible.
My rule is:
Without permission no climbing onto my bed.
Mainly hygiene.
Maybe it means
just from the outside
like after playing outside
or sweating from sports
you shouldn't just jump
onto someone's
sleeping area, right?
I wouldn't do that either.
Who's your roommate?
Me.
Then you remember.
He's a clean freak.
You？
I don't care.
Anything goes.
(stare)
I
I can't have my things
moved without asking.
That's similar to you.
Similar, same.
For me.
No shouting during rest
and to keep common areas clean.
Everyone's about the same.
I think we're all similar.
Here's a board.
I'll draw on it.
Do it here.
Need help.
I'll do it.
You hold this
hold the base
there should be a rod
at the back to prop it up.
You just had a rod?
I remember.
Like this
or like this
then turn it around.
You can sit and write.
No need to stand
that's tiring.
We're six, right?
One, two, three, four, five.
XY ROOM
What?
Rule Weird Tales.
Okay, first rule: anything goes.
Anything goes.
Second is me.
Wait, let me draw.
Third is...
I'm a little hard to draw right?
No.
I can already see a rough shape.
The first draft.
I like it.
You're messing with me.
And messing with me.
So what's the second?
I said one.
The first is "anything goes".
What's the second?
Love cleanliness.
And third?
What is the fourth？
No…
That's his rule?
Why aren't you speaking?
He's talking about you…
Because I don't know.
What he doesn't allow.
Then it's fine.
It feels like
"my rule is the rule".
My eyes are the ruler.
Then
no climbing onto my bed.
Okay, no unauthorized...
Okay, fourth?
Waner.
Just "anything goes".
Waner is quiet
but I think he's
a bit slow‑to‑warm.
Fifth is you.
Fifth is me now?
Yes, I'll draw a hat on you now.
OK.
Now Joel, your turn.
Hair is similar.
What's your requirement?
I don't have any.
How come no requirement again?
No limits.
"Anything goes" plus one, plus two.
He has no requirement.
You have no requirement.
I can also have none.
Now.
We only have one, two, three
I'll just add "Don't move
my stuff without asking".
That's it.
No matter what I talk about with Elio
he picks up on it right away.
It feels
great to me.
And I think
we'll get along well.
Give me a rule.
Keep quiet during sleep.
Keep quiet...
Do you guys want water?
I didn't drink.
No one?
Then I'll go get some.
Alright everyone.
Here's a task.
Today's PROJECT XY fridge
cannot provide premium ingredients.
Please choose two people
to go to a designated location
and complete the XY Drop Room mission.
To win a rich dinner
supply for everyone.
So we have to cook ourselves.
No, it says choose two
to the designated location
and play games.
Find stuff? Great.
So who's going?
I'll go.
Me too, I want to go.
Then you two go.
Let's go.
Wait for our good news.
We'll bring back beef.
Go for it.
Bring a ton of beef.
Tyler
I think he's very
outgoing.
On day one he can
joke with everyone.
Very natural.
I want to be
as cheerful as him.
We're waiting for your good news.
You must bring it back.
You have 30 seconds
to transport three ping‑pong balls
to the designated spot.
Failure means
no ingredients for today.
Beef，can we get it?
Let's try.
Ready.
Wait.
This cord is plugged in
we can't get past it.
We need someone to hold it
otherwise we'll pull the plug out.
OK?
Right.
Wait
let me get someone.
I'll go grab someone.
Okay.
I'll help Tyler with his hair.
I'll help him with his hair.
CH, let's go.
Go.
Go, quick.
Why me?
Come.
We have to play a game.
We can't do it alone.
It must have one person
to hold the hairdryer.
And finish the game.
We're coming.
I knew it.
Come.
Here's the rule.
We two can't do it.
The cord is short.
You hold this and stand there.
Blow, and we'll...
You need to control the ball.
It's up to you.
You can pre‑hold two balls in your hand.
No bending
to save time.
I'll hold two.
So we don't waste time.
We only have 30 seconds.
Let's try first.
Go. okay.
Three.
Two.
One.
Wait.
The wind is too strong.
Lower it.
This is the lowest.
Is this the lowest?
Aim a bit down.
Like this.
Like this?
Too low.
Like this, okay.
OK, go.
Nice.
That annoyed me.
Wait.
Let me see.
Let me move my hand forward a bit.
So you two can...
Alright.
No problem.
Three, two, one.
Right.
Go.
Up.
Faster, one, two.
Okay, go.
Three.
Two.
One.
Start.
Okay, slow down, one.
Up a bit.
Higher.
One, faster.
Slow down.
Steady first.
Three, two, one, Go.
Eyes!
Go.
How many seconds?
Thirty‑two.
Try again.
Off by two seconds.
Prepare.
Wait.
That 32‑second one doesn't count.
Do it again.
Three, two, one, go.
Go, go.
Go.
Next.
Three, two, one.
OK.
We're in sync.
Very fast, we can get four balls now.
Here we go.
How many seconds?
Seventeen.
Go.
We got it!
Bring in the eggplant.
And beef.
You go in first.
You go first, you take two things.
Ingredients are here.
Shrimp, mushrooms, onion, ginger, garlic
and green peppers
and beef.
Thanks, good work.
Take a rest.
I'll start cooking dinner.
Come on, wash the veggies.
I'll wash outside.
You just got back.
Go rest outside,
we'll handle it.
Really?
Yes, go rest.
You eat pork and beef?
Quietly getting to work.
Already eaten
I think it'll be tasty.
There are six
I'll help wash outside
I'll go wash outside.
Let me help you wash.
Need all of them washed?
I think enough
six eggplants.
And they said tomato scrambled eggs.
Tomato scrambled eggs?
Need peppers?
But why isn't the tomato washed?
Where's the tomato?
I'll get the tomato.
I said tomato scrambled eggs.
Why is there no tomato?
(The tomato is here)
Tomato is here.
Here it is.
I'll take them all.
Are you done washing?
Washed?
Yes.
You need tomatoes?
No.
They said they need tomatoes.
We're outside, we didn’t wash them yet.
He seems to need...
Who wants garlic?
Get a big plate.
Garlic?
Garlic, yes.
How many?
Can you peel two?
I want garlic too.
Want garlic, right?
I need!
Just peel one
one whole bulb.
Then chop it.
They want garlic.
You wash，I'll peel garlic.
OK.
Yes，I'll go peel garlic.
I'll peel the garlic.
How many does he want?
One whole bulb.
One whole?
All of it.
Do you use peppers?
Peppers?
He does.
I don't.
Honestly
I don't know what to talk about
so I'll just do practical things.
There's no minced pork.
I'll make noise.
Sorry, teachers.
Are you really chopping it by hand?
Yes, there's no minced meat.
There's no minced meat.
We're going to be sued.
You need minced meat?
Is there? Yes.
Really? Then what am I chopping?
Yes, it is.
(right-hand man)
Fine.
Is this minced meat?
Yes, it is.
Waner
he is very quiet,
but while we were cooking
he came over to ask me
if I needed help.
And then each time
after washing things
he asked me
if he can help me.
That's nice.
(Today's Chef)
You're washing outside.
Are these washed?
Yes, wait, I'll finish.
I'll bring them in.
This is Shanghai bok choy.
Not washed yet.
Not washed.
We have mushrooms.
There's more outside.
How do you want to cook this?
I think...
Stir‑fry with beef?
I think that works.
It’s really possible.
It's fine.
Old Xu.
After you're done
grab me a bowl.
Can you get me a bowl?
Sure.
How did you become "Old"?
Just rinse it.
Weren't you "Xiao" (young) just now?
Yes.
This morning you were Young
now you're Old Xu.
It's fine.
Elio.
Quite warm.
I feel he's...
actually a little like me
I've got a good impression of him.
Let's see if you've finished.
Yes, waiting for him.
OK.
You're going to stir‑fry the beef?
Beef is a must.
I really want beef.
We played so hard today,
just to get beef.
Stir‑fry beef.
If we don't eat it,
my heart will break.
"Spring and autumn pass
but this love never ends."
During summer breaks
I had vacations
I wanted to go out
and see life.
It was my first time learning to
cook at a restaurant.
I tried it.
I worked there about
half a month, it was tiring
but I learned to cook.
What are you washing?
Lettuce.
Here you go.
Can you wash shrimp?
Shrimp?
I think you don't need to wash
just blanch them
just blanch in water.
Who's eating this? You're eating it?
You're adding extra food for yourself?
I'm too hungry.
I'll eat a raw tomato.
How do you wash this?
Tear off leaves?
Probably not.
Just rub it.
Yes, wash it whole.
Shouldn't tear it.
Are you stir‑frying cucumber?
Want some?
Have a cucumber.
Would you like to eat cucumber?
Raw?
Yes.
Here.
Do you want?
But you two already split it.
It's okay
three pieces.
Great.
Okay.
I mainly want cucumber.
Can someone cut it?
Cut it.
I'll help, let me.
I'll put it here.
Okay.
You're cutting outside.
Cut into small pieces?
Yes, small pieces.
Yes.
Can we catch that chicken
back home?
(Let's add another dish)
There's a chicken outside.
It's going home already.
But it's in the coop.
Rock‑paper‑scissors
loser washes dishes.
I'll sit for a bit.
Can it hold both of us?
(Chill)
The plates and bowls.
(Cozy)
I washed, and then
I sat down.
I couldn't help in the kitchen anymore,
and everything was clean.
So I just stayed out of the way
and waited quietly.
While sitting in the
rocking chair, I thought
since I can't help much now
I'll just do the dishes later.
What's wrong?
Oh no, you cut yourself!
Who has a band‑aid?
Careful, that's a lot of blood.
I have band‑aids.
Use iodine first.
I have some.
Be careful.
That's a lot of blood.
Here, there is...
alcohol wipes.
Use an alcohol pad
disinfect first.
Oh my god.
Here.
That's a lot.
You cut deep into the flesh?
I think it's quite deep.
I was helping Elio cut green beans
for his stir‑fry.
And just like that,
I cut my thumb.
At that moment I thought.
Oh no.
It's okay, it's okay.
He's bleeding.
He really cut into the flesh
a lot of blood all over the floor.
Let me wipe it up first.
You can handle it yourself.
Here's a band‑aid
just stick it on.
I shouldn't have asked
him to cut the beans.
When I was just cooking
it was then that
I asked him to give me a hand
and then he cut himself
I feel guilty.
I've washed it.
Is it right?
Let me see.
Wait, OK.
Bandage.
I need some gauze.
Okay, that's it.
Clean up the floor.
So much blood.
I'll do it.
Does it still hurt?
I think you need a tetanus shot.
That cut looks deep, bleeding
and might need stitches.
(Next Episode)
Who?
Who is it?
It's a task box here.
Within 15 minutes,
write the name of the person you feel most
drawn to and why. Everyone only gets one vote.
If it were me
I'd probably cry.
Honestly, I'm not surprised.
I had that feeling, intuition.
It's hard.
Only the first day.
I actually focused on
three people.
One is Elio.
Joel,
and...
I mainly looked for
qualities I rarely see.
Zero votes.
Two votes.
One vote.
No one so far.
(What's the first vote results?)
"Project XY"